Correctional Association of New York; Records apap014
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED], 1967-1983; 5; 1.66 cubic ft.
  - Ombudsman - News Clippings [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - Ombudsman - Committee [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - Ombudsman - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - Ombudsman - Fundraising [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
  - Ombudsman - Program Agencies [RESTRICTED], 1969-1972 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
  - Ombudsman - Program Agencies [RESTRICTED], 1971-1978 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
  - Ombudsman - Proposal [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 2 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Proposal - Alcoholism Program [RESTRICTED], ca. 1980 (Box 2 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Proposal - Lengthy Detention Program [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 2 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Social Services [RESTRICTED], 1977-1981 (Box 2 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Social Services - Correspondence - Friedlander, Shelley (Director) [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 2 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Social Services - Correspondence - Friedlander, Shelley [RESTRICTED], 1977; 2 folders (Box 2 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Social Services - Correspondence - Friedlander, Shelley [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 3 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Social Services - Correspondence - Friedlander, Shelley [RESTRICTED], 1979-1981 (Box 3 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Social Services - Reports [RESTRICTED], 1973-1981 (Box 3 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
- Project Files [RESTRICTED], 1974-1988; 6; 3.33 cubic ft.
  This series consists of material created or collected by Correctional Association staffers and board members engaged in short-term projects designed to produce written reports about various aspects of the correctional system; copies of many of these reports are included. Of particular interest are the Case Histories Project (1983-1985), Idle Time Project (1981-1985), and the Prison and Jail Conditions Project (1982-1986), which entailed extensive surveys of conditions and inmate programs available in New York State correctional facilities and generated correspondence and other material from inmates. Also of note is the Prison Mental Hygiene Project (1985-1988) that documents the programs and resources then available to prisoners with mental illness and developmental disabilities. Two of the projects, the State Planning Project (1981-1982) and the Prison Overcrowding Project (1982-1984), concern crowding in prisons and alternatives to new prison construction. This series also contains material generated in connection with the AIDS in Prison Project (1985-1988), the Budget Education Project (1983-1985), the Latino Project (1985-1988), and proposals for several other projects that the Association did not complete.
  - AIDS in Prison Project [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - AIDS in Prison Project [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Budget Education Project [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Budget Education Project [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Budget Education Project - Allies [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Budget Education Project - Allies - State and City [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Budget Education Project - Batch Application [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Budget Education Project - Calculations [RESTRICTED], 1978-1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Budget Education Project - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Budget Education Project - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Budget Education Project - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1983-1986 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Budget Education Project - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Budget Education Project - Correspondence - New York City Office of Management and Budget [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Budget Education Project - Cost of Corrections [RESTRICTED], 1980-1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Budget Education Project - Counterbudget [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Budget Education Project - "Hidden Costs of Incarceration" - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Budget Education Project - "Hidden Costs of Incarceration" - Media [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Budget Education Project - Matthias, Robert [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Budget Education Project - New York City Jail Crisis [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Budget Education Project - New York City Jail Crisis - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Budget Education Project - New York City Jail Crisis - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Budget Education Project - Monthly Financial Reports [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Budget Education Project - Number 2 [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Budget Education Project - Prison Operating Costs [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Budget Education Project - Prison Operating Costs - Press Release [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Budget Education Project - Proposal [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Budget Education Project - Proposal [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - Budget Education Project - Public Safety [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - Budget Education Project - Statewide Youth Advocates [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - Budget Education Project - Steelman, Diane [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - Budget Education Project - Steelman, Diane - Reports [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - Budget Education Project - What Price Safety? [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
  - Case Histories Project [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
  - Case Histories Project - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
  - Case Histories Project - Do They Belong in Prison? [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
  - Case Histories Project - Do They Belong in Prison? - Advance Copies Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
  - Case Histories Project - Do They Belong in Prison - Advance Copy [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
  - Case Histories Project - Proposal [RESTRICTED], 1982/1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
  - Case Histories Project - Release Forms [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)
  - Idle Time Project - "Doing Idle Time" [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 40)
  - Idle Time Project - "Doing Idle Time" - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 41)
  - Idle Time Project - "Doing Idle Time" - Interviews and Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 42)
  - Idle Time Project - "Doing Idle Time" - Report Mailing List and Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 43)
  - Idle Time Project - "Doing Idle Time" - Press Coverage [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 44)
  - Idle Time Project - Other States [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 45)
  - Idle Time Project - Proposal and Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 46)
  - Idle Time Project - Prison Alcohol Programs [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 47)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Adirondack Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 48)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Albion [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 49)
  - Idle Time Project - Arthur Kill [RESTRICTED], 1980-1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 50)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Auburn [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 51)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Bayview [RESTRICTED], 1983-1986 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 52)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Bedford Hills [RESTRICTED], 1983-1986 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 53)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Clinton [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 54)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Collins [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 55)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Coxsackie [RESTRICTED], 1981-1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 56)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Downstate [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 57)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Eastern/Naponoch [RESTRICTED], 1982-1986 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 58)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Elmira [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 59)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Fishkill [RESTRICTED], 1981-1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 60)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Great Meadow/Comstock [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 61)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Green Haven [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 62)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Groveland [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 63)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Hudson [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 64)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Lincoln [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 65)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Long Island/Pilgrim/Brentwood [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 66)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Mid - Orange [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 67)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Ogdensburg [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 68)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Otisville [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 69)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Sing Sing (Ossining) [RESTRICTED], 1922-1984 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 70)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Survey - Taconic [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 71)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Wallkill [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 72)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Watertown [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 73)
  - Idle Time Project - Survey - Woodburne [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 74)
  - Latino Project [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Latino Project - Impact of Prison on Inner City Black and Latino Communities [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - New York City Pretrial Detention Project [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project [RESTRICTED], 1982-1986 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project - Director Search [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project - Meeting Announcements [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project - Neglected Population - Bayview Advisory Board [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project - Neglected Population - Commissioner's Response [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project - Neglected Population - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project - Neglected Population - Requests [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project - Neglected Population: Women Prisoners at Bayview [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project - Outline [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project - Policymaker Education [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project - Potler, Cathy - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project - Potler, Cathy - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project - Potler, Cathy - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project - Potler, Cathy - Reports [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project - Proposal and Budget [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project - Proposal [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project - State of the Prisons [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Prison and Jail Conditions Project - Third Year Proposal [RESTRICTED], 1986? (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene and AIDS Projects - Public Officials [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Alliance for the Mentally Ill of Westchester County [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - AMI Interviews [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Attica - Eng v. Smith [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Background Reports [RESTRICTED], 1979-1981 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Crime and Mental Illness [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Deinstitutionalization [RESTRICTED], 1978-1987 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Epilepsy [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Ex-mental Patients in Criminal Justice System [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - General [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Grants and Budget [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Media [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mental Health Alternatives to Incarceration Program [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mental Health Literature [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mental Health - Westchester County [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners [RESTRICTED], 1979-1987 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Commission on Quality of Care for the Mentally Disabled [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 40)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Connelly/Feldman Report [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 41)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Feldman Report [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 42)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - H.E.L.P. and Other Family Groups [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 43)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Legislative Hearings [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 44)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Meeting [RESTRICTED], ca. 1985 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 45)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Mentally Impaired in New York's Prisons [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 46)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Mentally Impaired in New York's Prisons - Reactions to Report [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 47)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Other State Programs [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 48)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Prisoners' Legal Services, etc. [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 49)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Problems and Treatment [RESTRICTED], 1980-1985 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 50)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Report Mailing List, etc. [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 51)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Retarded Offenders [RESTRICTED], 1973-1982 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 52)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Steelman, Diane - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 53)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Texas - Ruiz v. Estelle [RESTRICTED], 1984-1986 (Box 2 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 54)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - New York City Jails [RESTRICTED], 1983-1986 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - New York State Mental Health System [RESTRICTED], 1984-1987 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - New York State Office of Mental Health Forensic Services [RESTRICTED], 1983-1986 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - New York State Office of Mental Health Forensic Services [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - New York State Office of Mental Health - Level of Care Study [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - New York State Prisons - General [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Notes [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Other Research Projects [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Outline [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Parole [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Proposal Summary [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Retreat [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Retreat/Colloquium [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Attica [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Auburn [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Bedford Hills [RESTRICTED], 1981-1987 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Central New York Psychiatric Center [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Clinton [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Downstate [RESTRICTED], 1982-1986 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Elmira [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Fishkill [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Great Meadow/Comstock [RESTRICTED], 1982-1986 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Green Haven [RESTRICTED], 1978-1985 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Sing Sing (Ossining) [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Sullivan [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Wende [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - TASC (Treatment Alternatives to Street Crime, Westchester County) [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - TASC [RESTRICTED], 1988? (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - TASC - Interview Questions [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 3 (6-Project Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)